# A G U S T I N C O R D O B A

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### CONTACT

- (351) 7895201
- AGUSTIN.CORDOBA.WORK@GMAIL.COM
- O CORDOBA. CORDOBA
- 💡 NACIONALITY: ARGENTINA
- HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/AGUSWORK
- in HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/AGUSTIN-MARIA-CORDOBA/
- HTTPS://PORTFOLIO-AGUSTIN-CORDOBA.VERCEL.APP/ES

### SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS / SCSS / Tailwind
- JavaScript / Typescript
- React / Next.Js / Vue.js
- Redux / Zustand / Vuex
- Figma / Notion
- PHP / Laravel
- JEST / TestingLibrary
- Git GitHub
- Docker / AWS
- SCRUM / CRUD / SOLID
- Node.Js / Nest.JS
- MongoDB / PostgreSQL / SQL

## AVAILABILITY: FULLTIME

### LANGHAGES

**IELTS (2024)** 

UNIVERSIDAD BLAS PASCAL RESULT: C1

FIRST CERTIFICATE B2 (2017)

INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL OF ENGLISH LA FALDA, CORDOBA RESULT: PASS WITH MERIT

### PROFILE

Front End Developer with experience in personal and professional work, I have two years of professional experience in freelance work from landing pages to MFE's, currently specializing in React, NextJs, Node, MongoDB and Docker. I also work as Fullstack since my professional work demanded it and I could quickly develop and resolve those issues. I also have experience with PHP, MySql, Laravel and some knowledge in Java and Python.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### KRAIZZ DIGITAL CO. (2023 - 24

FRONT-END DEVELOPER . WORKING METHOD: SCRUM - SOLID. PROGRAMS: REACT, NEXT.JS, SCSS, JEST. MORE INFORMATION IN MY PORTFOLIO

### PROPULZ (2022 - 24)

FRONT-END DEVELOPER .
WORKING METHOD: SCRUM - SOLID.
PROGRAMS: REACT, NEXT.JS, SCSS.
MORE INFORMATION IN MY PORTFOLIO

### LILLEGROUP (2022- 24)

PSR - PATIENT SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE
ANSWERING SERVICE FOR CAPITAL CARDIOLOGY ASSOCIATES
DEALING WITH CUSTOMER SERVICE
SCHEDULING TASKS
ON DEMAND EMERGENCIES

### SYNTESIS (2021)

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER . WORKING METHOD: SCRUM. PROGRAMS: PHP, LARAVEL, TAILWIND.

## EDUCATION

### **REACT - NEXTJS DEVELOPER (2021 - 22)**

UDEMY ACADEMY FINAL WORK SCORE: 9

### IAVA SCRIPT DEVELOPER (2021)

CODERHOUSE ACADEMY FINAL WORK SCORE: 10

### **BACHELOR OF PSYCHOLOGY (2019 - TODAY)**

NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF CÓRDOBA. COURSE: 4TH YEAR